[
  {
    "questionNo": "Q1",
    "question": "If 'A' = 1, 'B' = 3, 'C' = 5, etc., what is the sum of the letters in the word \"NURSE\"?",
    "options": [
      "135",
      "149",
      "153",
      "210"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q2",
    "question": "In a code, 'PLANT' is written as $@27- and YIELD as '&64@%'. How is 'DELAY' written?",
    "options": [
      "%4@2&",
      "%64@2",
      "64@%2",
      "@%64"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q3",
    "question": "In a certain code, if 'RED' is written as TGF. How is PINK written in that code?",
    "options": [
      "RKPN",
      "REVB",
      "MKLJ",
      "RKPM"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q4",
    "question": "If 'apple' is called 'lemon', 'lemon' is called 'cake', and so on, which one is sour in taste?",
    "options": [
      "SANDWICH",
      "LEMON",
      "APPLE",
      "CAKE"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q5",
    "question": "In a certain code, COMMUNICATION is written as NOITACINUMMOC. Which letter will be in the 6th place when MOUNTAIN is written in that code?",
    "options": [
      "U",
      "P",
      "I",
      "O"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q6",
    "question": "In a certain code, if 'JUNE' = 50, then what will 'JULY' equal to?",
    "options": [
      "60",
      "68",
      "62",
      "58"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q7",
    "question": "In a certain code, 169 means YOU ARE GOOD and 764 means WHERE ARE FLOWERS. What is the code for FLOWERS ARE GOOD?",
    "options": [
      "469",
      "389",
      "981",
      "641"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q8",
    "question": "In a certain code, 're ti ku' means 'eating is necessary'. What is the code for 'necessary'?",
    "options": [
      "ti",
      "re",
      "Sa",
      "ku"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q9",
    "question": "If A = E, B = F, C = G and H = L, how will the word COME be written in this code?",
    "options": [
      "GSQI",
      "BSHM",
      "ISBE",
      "TNME"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q10",
    "question": "If RAMESH = AREMHS, then AARYAN = ?",
    "options": [
      "AZYOPN",
      "ARPMNA",
      "ARYYMN",
      "AAYRNA"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q11",
    "question": "If RABBIT= IZYYRG, then CAT = ?",
    "options": [
      "XZL",
      "XZG",
      "XZB",
      "ZBP"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q12",
    "question": "In a certain code 'ELEPHANT' is written as 'LEPEAHTN'. How is 'MONKEY' written in that code?",
    "options": [
      "OMKNYE",
      "ONMNKY",
      "NMKYOK",
      "MNKOYE"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q13",
    "question": "In certain code 'MONTH' is written as 'IUOPN'. Then how would 'YEAR' be written in that code?",
    "options": [
      "ISND",
      "SBFZ",
      "OFME",
      "PJMW"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q14",
    "question": "In a certain code 'GLASS' is written as 'JODVV'. How is 'CUP' written in that code?",
    "options": [
      "HNE",
      "PKB",
      "FXS",
      "VSO"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q15",
    "question": "If NOTEBOOK is written as ONUDCNPJ, how is PENCIL written?",
    "options": [
      "QDOBJK",
      "JEJWKS",
      "POWMS",
      "HEBAIN"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q16",
    "question": "In a certain language 'PROFIT' is written as 'OQQSNPEGHJSU'. How is 'LOSS' written in that language?",
    "options": [
      "HNRTSMN",
      "MNATWTP",
      "FXBSNATE",
      "KMNPRTRT"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q17",
    "question": "If CUPCAKE = ECMGEWR, what is SANDWICH?",
    "options": [
      "YKEJUCPF",
      "HEIPNDEY",
      "BEIWKHYI",
      "INSHJWPJ"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q18",
    "question": "If JUNE is the same as LXQG, what is JULY?",
    "options": [
      "LAUB",
      "LXOA",
      "ANIW",
      "MNOW"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q19",
    "question": "In a code language, '134' means 'NICE AND LOVELY', '478' means 'WEAR NICE CLOTHES' and '729' means 'CLOTHES ARE PRETTY', then which code means 'WEAR' in that code language?",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "7",
      "8",
      "1"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "questionNo": "Q20",
    "question": "In certain code 'TIGER' is written as 'QDFHS'. How is 'FISH' written in that code?",
    "options": [
      "GRHE",
      "GREH",
      "GHRE",
      "GEHR"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  }
]
